Oh, it feels so good.
あー、めちゃめちゃ気持ちいい
It blew up a lot.
めっちゃ吹いちゃった
Oh no!
あー、やばい!
Something like this voice,
なんかこの声、
I'll take some pictures of this.
なんか 撮っちゃうね、これ
I wanted to take a picture of the room soon.
早くお部屋撮りたかった
I want you to prepare.
準備してほしいな
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
What can I do?
何していいですか?
Can I do the same?
同じようにしていい?
No more teasing.
もうじらしなし
I am often told that my pussy is beautiful.
マンコ綺麗ってよく言われます
thank you.
ありがとう
Because everyone uses it beautifully.
みんなが綺麗に使ってくれるからだよ
Oh, it feels so good.
あー、めちゃめちゃ気持ちいい
huge?
でっかい?
What?
何が?
It's not like her pussy is loose.
マンコガバガバじゃないもん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
You can enter it until today.
今日まで入れていいよ
It's okay to jerk off.
シコシコしていいよ
I've been waiting so let's hurry.
待たしちゃったから早くしよう
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
It's crazy, it might actually come out today.
やばい、マジ今日すぐ出ちゃうかもしれない
Let me pay for Minami's pussy.
南のマンコ払わせて
After my dad left for rap.
ラップでパパは行ったあとね
Just a little more.
もうちょいね
You can drink it.
飲みていいよ
Ah, great.
あー、いばーい
Let's hurry.
早 くしちゃおう
I think I'll go right away today.
今日マジですぐ行っちゃうと思う
terrible.
やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
terrible.
やばい
After all, I went there a lot.
やっぱりいっぱい行っちゃったんよ
Suddenly.
いきなり
Do you want to look down?
うつんだい見たいの?
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I think I'll try it out.
うつんだいしようかな
For now, the pussy.
とりあえずマンコが
appear?
見える?
It's soaking wet though.
びしょびしょなんだけど
Look.
ほら
Sleep, sleep.
寝る寝る
This is dangerous.
やばいよもう
It blew up a lot.
めっちゃ吹いちゃった
Hey, Minami is a good girl.
ね、南いい子だよね
Really.
本当にね
Good.
よいしょ
I guess I'll just hang out.
うつんだいでしようかな
Just a little more.
もうちょい
ah.
あー
Ah, sleep.
あー、寝て
Same live.
同じライブ
You can't see my throat dick.
喉チンコなんか見えないでしょ
Do you want to put dick in it?
チンチン入れたい?
You can put the safe in your mouth.
口にセーフ出していいよ
Shall we have a quick chat?
つぼつぼしようか
Do you want to see a close-up of your pussy?
マンコアップ見たいの?
If you get your pussy up, if you get your pussy up,
マンコアップしたら、 マンコアップしたら、
You know, there's some kind of hair on it.
あれね、なんか髪の毛ついてる
If you close up your pussy, it will jibobo.
マンコアップしたらじぼぼね
Okay.
よし
Shall we jibobo?
じぼぼしようか
Wait a moment, I'll make a par.
パーするからちょっと待って
That's right.
そうやな
You added too much.
量つけすぎたよね
Are you still holding back, Minami?
まだ我慢してんの、南が
That Minami is holding back his cock,
あの南がチンポを我慢しているのよ、
still.
まだ
It became slimy.
ヌルヌルなっちゃった
It's par.
パーです
Don't be jittery.
じぼぼぼするな
I want to wipe the tide once.
一回潮拭きたい
ERROR
潮拭いていい?
I'm coming.
来ちゃうんだわ
Wait already.
もう待って
Oh no, it came out again.
やばい、まためっちゃ出ちゃった
That's dangerous.
やばくね
It's like I want to wipe the tide.
潮拭いたいのみたいな
This is terrible.
やばいよ
This is the one that I can't blow very well.
これがあんま吹けないやつなんでね、
I forgot the skin-colored one I always use,
いつも使ってる肌色のやつを忘れちゃって、
I'll bring it.
持ってくるの
That's better though.
あれのほうがいいんだけどさ
Where do you go after wiping the tide?
潮拭いてどこに?
I'll wipe the tide.
潮拭するね
I don't really feel like it, and it hurts,
なんかあんま気持ちがないし、 痛いんだけど、
this.
これ
The usual one is good.
いつものやつがいい
I can't do this.
これできない
My dick is too hard so I can't do it.
チンチンが硬すぎてできない
This is impossible.
これ無理
You mean it's not on camera?
カメラ上じゃないってこと?
This is impossible, so can I stop?
これ無理だからやめていいですか?
I don't feel like it at all.
全然気持ちがない
It's called half cut.
半切れっていう
I don't really like tide wipes.
潮拭そんな好きじゃないしな
I prefer to do it normally with chin chin.
普通にチンチンでやるほうが好きだわ
Can I wipe the tide?
潮拭していい?
It's no good wiping the tide.
潮拭るのがダメなの
dislike.
嫌い
It hurts and it hurts.
痛くて痛い
Someone mess with Chikugi.
チクギ誰かいじってよ
It's only just begun.
まだ始まったばっかだよね
I've been doing it for an hour.
1時間やってるよ
I think it will take about another hour.
あと1時間くらいやると思う
perhaps.
多分
I still peed, so wait a minute.
まだおしっこしたから、 ちょっと待ってて
Are you the type of person who feels good with chikugi?
チクギで気持ちよくなれるタイプの人ですか?
Chikugi prefers someone to touch her.
チクギは誰かに触ってもらうほうが好き
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Wait till you go.
行くまで待って
It came out soon.
もうすぐ出た
It's a bit serious.
ちょっとマジでやばい
It looks like a puddle.
水たまりみたいになってる
I'm home.
ただいま
I'm not going out anymore.
もう出ない
I'll go out after drinking tea.
お茶飲んだら出るよ